Guide to the Allen Ginsberg film and video archive, 1983 - 1996
Department of Special Collections
Allen Ginsberg film and video archive,
1983 - 1996
Mss Media 0004
Aronson, Jerry
154 videotapes
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections and University Archives.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
None.
Provenance
Purchased, 2001.
Container List
- Allen Ginsberg Performance, Part I. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Time in: 0:00:00 Time out: 0:22:45 Total Time: 22m 45s Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Naropa Institute, Boulder, CO, May 27, 1983. Begins with shots of audience, continues with Peter and Allen playing music together and ends with an interview of Allen outside his Boulder house.
  - Shots of audience.
    Time in: 0:00:00 Time out: 0:09:12 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In Naropa auditorium.
  - Peter Orlovsky and Allen Ginsberg playing music.
    Time in: 0:09:15 Time out: 0:11:55 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  - Allen Ginsberg Interview.
    Time in: 0:11:56 Time out: 0:22:45 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    End of interview on steps at Allen's house on Bluff St. in Boulder.
- Allen Ginsberg Performance, Part II. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Time in: 0:00:00 Time out: 0:21:20 Total Time: 21m 20s Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Naropa Institute, Boulder, CO, May 27, 1983. Ginsberg performs with a small band and reads poetry with music backup. Ginsberg later chants a mantra.
  - "Why I Meditate".
    Time in: 2:05:13 Time out: 2:08:53 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg sings with a small back-up band.
  - "Put Down That Cigarette Rag (Don't Smoke)".
    Time in: 2:09:05 Time out: 2:14:26 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  - Mantra.
    Time in: 2:16:52 Time out: 2:19:00 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg chants with a small back-up band.
  - "September on Jessore Road".
    Time in: 2:19:02 Time out: 2:21:28 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
- Allen Ginsberg Performance, Part III. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Time in: 0:00:00 Time out: 0:14:47 Total Time: 14m 47s Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Naropa Institute, Boulder, CO, May 27, 1983. More of Ginsberg singing with his back-up band.
  - "Do the Meditation Rock".
    Time in: 1:11:02 Time out: 1:14:44 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg sings with a small back-up band. (Jump at 1:12:45)
- Allen Ginsberg Interview, Part I. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Time in: 0:00:00 Time out: 0:22:20 Total Time: 22m 20s Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Ginsberg's home on Bluff Street in Boulder, CO, May 28, 1983. Interview takes place outside.
  - Peter Orlovsky working on garden outside.
    Time in: 0:00:00 Time out: 0:04:21 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    General outdoor ambient sound.
  - Allen Ginsberg walking and interview on steps outside.
    Time in: 0:06:13 Time out: 0:22:20 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg outside his house on Bluff St. in Boulder, CO.
- Allen Ginsberg Interview, Part II. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Time in: 0:00:00 Time out: 0:22:23 Total Time: 22m 23s Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Ginsberg's home in Boulder, CO May 28, 1983. Ginsberg outside his house on Bluff St.
- Allen Ginsberg Interview, Part III. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Time in: 0:00:00 Time out: 0:22:54 Total Time: 22m 54s Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
- Allen Ginsberg Interview, Part IV. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Time in: 0:00:00 Time out: 0:22:11 Total Time: 22m 11s Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Ginsberg's home in Boulder, CO May 28, 1983. Ginsberg in the living room of his Bluff Street. residence, reading his own poetry, explaining and analyzing highlights of poems.
  - "King of May".
    Time in: 0:13:34 Time out: 0:18:26 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg reads his own poetry.
  - "Kaddish".
    Time in: 0:19:09 Time out: 0:21:01 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
- Allen Ginsberg Interview, Part V. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Time in: 0:00:00 Time out: 0:22:55 Total Time: 22m 55s Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  - "Father Death Blues" (spoken).
    Time in: 0:01:05 Time out: 0:03:07 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    A spoken version of Ginsberg's blues tune.
  - "Howl".
    Time in: 0:05:18 Time out: 0:07:07 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  - About "Howl".
    Time in: 0:07:08 Time out: 0:11:52 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg explains his poem.
  - "On Neal's Ashes".
    Time in: 0:13:31 Time out: 0:14:17 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  - Interview with Allen Ginsberg.
    Time in: 0:20:23 Time out: 0:22:55 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Allen discusses the '68 Chicago Convention.
- Excerpt from Don't Look Back. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Time in: 1:00:00 Time out: 1:05:00 Total Time: 8m 54s Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Excerpt from D.A. Pennebaker's feature documentary film on Bob Dylan, Don't Look Back.
  - Don't Look Back: "Subterranean Homesick Blues", the opening scene of the film. Take I
    Time in: 1:00:00 Time out: 1:02:28 Total Time: 2m 28s Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Dylan in foreground, flipping through cue-cards with lyrics, Ginsberg in background. Full-screen version.
  - Don't Look Back: "Subterranean Homesick Blues", the opening scene of the film. Take II
    Time in: 1:02:30 Time out: 1:05:00 Total Time: 2m 30s Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Dylan holds signs up, illustrating the song's text. This version is letter-boxed, where it is easier to see Ginsberg in the background.
- Ginsberg Excerpts from Renaldo and Clara. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Time in: 10:00:00 Time out: 10:17:16 Total Time: 17m 6s Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Excerpts from Bob Dylan's feature documentary of his 1975 Rolling Thunder Review entitled, Renaldo and Clara.
  - Ginsberg at Jewish Old Folks' Home.
    Time in: 10:00:30 Time out: 10:01:21 Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg is on stage being introduced to the audience.
  - Ginsberg Singing Blake Poem.
    Time in: 10:01:21 Time out: 10:02:54 Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg sings "All the Hills Echoed" accompanied by a woman guitarist.
  - Ginsberg with Dylan and Rolling Thunder Review.
    Time in: 10:02:55 Time out: 10:04:42 Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    All performers sing and dance together next to a lake.
  - Ginsberg at Jewish Old Folks' Home.
    Time in: 10:04:43 Time out: 10:06:58 Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg reads a poem.
  - Ginsberg with Fortune Teller.
    Time in: 10:06:59 Time out: 10:08:49 Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg gets his palms read by an old fortune teller.
  - Ginsberg with Dylan at Kerouac's Grave.
    Time in: 10:08:50 Time out: 10:10:40 Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg and Dylan reminisce by Kerouac's grave.
  - Ginsberg Shaving Beard.
    Time in: 10:10:40 Time out: 10:11:50 Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    A woman shaves off Ginsberg's beard.
  - Ginsberg with Dylan at Kerouac's Grave.
    Time in: 10:11:50 Time out: 10:13:02 Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  - Ginsberg with Dylan in Schoolyard.
    Time in: 10:13:03 Time out: 10:14:09 Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg and Dylan chat about God with some children playing in a schoolyard.
  - Ginsberg Dancing.
    Time in: 10:14:10 Time out: 10:17:16 Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg dancing with young female partner to modern music at the Jewish old folks' home.
- Excerpt from Renaldo and Clara: Whore house scene. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  Time in: 0:00:00 Time out: 0:03:30 Total Time: 3m 30s Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Excerpt from Bob Dylan's documentary of his 1975 Rolling Thunder Review, Renaldo and Clara. Ginsberg and friends, including Joan Baez, Anne Waldman and others playing a whorehouse scene.
- Allen Ginsberg Interview. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  Time in: 11:00:23 Time out: 11:22:50 Total Time: 22m 48s Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  September 1, 1984. Interview by John Miglietta with Ginsberg sitting outside. Ignore the color bars: 11:05:52-11:06:35.
- 25th Anniversary Reading of "Howl". (Box 2, Folder 13)
  Time in: 13:00:00 Time out: 13:22:13 Total Time: 22m 13s Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Columbia University, New York City, 1981. Ginsberg has returned to his alma mater to read "Howl" and other poems.
  - Pre-show.
    Time in: 13:00:19 Time out: 13:11:35 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg discusses "Howl" with Peter Goldfarb. The sound is not good until 13:02:23.
  - Introduction by Anne Waldman.
    Time in: 13:12:56 Time out: 13:18:10 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    First take, not as good as second take.
  - Allen introduces the program.
    Time in: 13:18:26 Time out: 13:24:10 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  - Introduction by Anne Waldman, second transfer.
    Time in: 13:24:12 Time out: 13:29:42 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Second take, better transfer.
  - Allen introduces program, second transfer.
    Time in: 13:29:43 Time out: 13:32:13 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
- 25th Anniversary Reading of "Howl". (Box 2, Folder 14)
  Time in: 14:00:02 Time out: 14:17:51 Total Time: 17m 51s Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Columbia University, New York City, 1981. Ginsberg reading "Howl", Stanza I. Time Code and image jump near the end of the tape.
- 25th Anniversary Reading of "Howl". (Box 2, Folder 15)
  Time in: 15:00:38 Time out: 15:19:01 Total Time: 11m 5s Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Columbia University, New York City, 1981. Ginsberg reads two poems, "America" and "Many Loves" with jumps in the Time Code throughout.
  - "America", beginning of poem.
    Time in: 15:00:38 Time out: 15:02:28 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    First stanza, mostly out of focus and shaky, but good sound.
  - "America", end of poem.
    Time in: 15:02:34 Time out: 15:04:24 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Image partially usable and the sound is good. The last line: "... queer shoulder to the wheel."
  - "Many Loves".
    Time in: 15:13:08 Time out: 15:19:01 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg reads the portion of the poem that is a love song for Neal Cassady.
- 25th Anniversary Reading of "Howl". (Box 2, Folder 16)
  Time in: 18:00:48 Time out: 18:20:17 Total Time: 17m 30s Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Columbia University, New York City, 1981. Peter Goldfarb interviews Ginsberg on stage at Columbia in 1981. Anne Waldman introduces "Howl."
  - Goldfarb interview.
    Time in: 18:00:48 Time out: 18:10:31 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Hand-held with shaky camera and sound problems. However, some material is definitely useable. Stage Left.
  - Anne Waldman introduction.
    Time in: 18:12:55 Time out: 18:18:02 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Focus problems and shaky throughout, sound mostly useable. Stage Left.
- 25th Anniversary Reading of "Howl"; Ginsberg Interview. (Box 2, Folder 17)
  Time in: 19:00:55 Time out: 6:20:58 Total Time: 20m 27s Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Columbia University, New York City, 1981. Actual reading of poem, "Howl". Stage Left and Right as camera moves unthinkingly between stage and audience. Also a brief excerpt from 1983 of Ginsberg's interview on the steps in his back yard in Boulder, CO.
  - "Howl" reading.
    Time in: 19:00:55 Time out: 19:05:32 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Stage Left. Camera begins to move near end of section. Picture cuts and sound continues.
  - "Howl" reading continues.
    Time in: 19:05:52 Time out: 19:13:54 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Stage Right. Image shaky, but there are some useable shots of Ginsberg and of the audience. The sound is excellent.
  - Ginsberg interview on the steps of his house in Boulder, CO, 1983.
    Time in: 6:14:05 Time out: 6:20:58 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg comments on meditation, high school loves and a very important description of his coming out to Kerouac at Columbia University.
- 25th Anniversary Reading of "Howl". (Box 2, Folder 18)
  Time in: 20:00:40 Time out: 20:20:24 Total Time: 20m 8s Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Columbia University, New York City, 1981. Ginsberg reads the end of "Howl", "Footnote to Howl" and "Sunflower Sutra".
  - Last portion of "Howl".
    Time in: 20:00:40 Time out: 20:07:08 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Stage Right. Almost all usable.
  - Last portion of "Howl".
    Time in: 20:07:08 Time out: 20:10:20 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Stage Left. Shakier image, but good sound as well as good shots of the audience.
  - "Footnote to Howl".
    Time in: 20:10:50 Time out: 20:13:45 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Stage Left. Useable footage.
  - "Sunflower Sutra".
    Time in: 20:14:20 Time out: 20:20:24 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Stage Left. Image quality useable. Sound usable and audience shots usable.
- Kerouac Conference. (Box 2, Folder 19)
  Time in: 1:00:28 Time out: 1:18:28 Total Time: 18m 0s Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Naropa Institute, Boulder, CO, 1982. Includes interviews with Ferlinghetti, Edie Kerouac Parker, David Amram, McClure, Joyce Johnson, Corso, and Kesey.
  - Allen Ginsberg sings with band.
    Time in: 1:00:28 Time out: 1:01:27 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Sings "Do the Meditation", great version!
  - Lawrence Ferlinghetti reads a poem.
    Time in: 1:01:27 Time out: 1:01:44 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ferlinghetti reads a poem by Kerouac.
  - Interview with Edie Kerouac Parker.
    Time in: 1:01:44 Time out: 1:03:02 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Kerouac's first wife fondly remembers Jack Kerouac as a loving man.
  - Interview with David Amram.
    Time in: 1:03:02 Time out: 1:04:40 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Amram talks about music and the Kerouac beat in his work.
  - Interview with Michael McClure.
    Time in: 1:04:40 Time out: 1:05:21 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    McClure describes Kerouac's writing and how it influenced those around him.
  - Interview with Edie Parker.
    Time in: 1:05:21 Time out: 1:06:15 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    More talk about Kerouac and their relationship.
  - Michael McClure reading a Kerouac poem.
    Time in: 1:06:15 Time out: 1:08:23 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    McClure reads one of Kerouac's poems to describe his style.
  - Joyce Johnson interview.
    Time in: 1:08:23 Time out: 1:11:00 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Johnson describes her first meeting with Jack, a blind date set up by Ginsberg.
  - Panel moderator.
    Time in: 1:11:00 Time out: 1:12:24 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    The moderator keeps the women's panel moving by asking a question about Jack's intimacy factor.
  - Gregory Corso interview.
    Time in: 1:12:24 Time out: 1:14:49 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Corso makes a humorous comment about Ginsberg and Kerouac.
  - Ferlinghetti reading a poem of Kerouac's.
    Time in: 1:14:49 Time out: 1:18:28 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ferlinghetti reads one of his favorite poems written by Kerouac.
- Kerouac Conference: Interviews with Michael McClure, Carolyn Cassady and Gregory Corso. (Box 2, Folder 20)
  Time in: 2:00:27 Time out: 2:22:04 Total Time: 21m 0s Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Interviews at the 1982 Kerouac Conference at the Naropa Institute, Boulder, CO.
  - Michael McClure interview.
    Time in: 2:00:27 Time out: 2:07:37 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    McClure talks about Kerouac and the other Beats and their influence on younger poets.
  - Carolyn Cassady interview.
    Time in: 2:07:37 Time out: 2:15:58 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Carolyn Cassady describes being the woman between Neal Cassady and Jack Kerouac and how enjoyable it was.
  - Gregory Corso interview.
    Time in: 2:15:58 Time out: 2:22:04 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Corso talks about the meetings and ideas that occurred between Kerouac, Ginsberg and Burroughs.
- Interview with David Amram. (Box 3, Folder 21)
  Time in: 3:00:43 Time out: 3:25:49 Total Time: 25m 6s Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Kerouac Conference, Naropa Institute, Boulder, CO, 1982. Peter Goldfarb interviews David Amram about musical rhythm and the Beats.
- Panel: Kerouac and His Women, Part I. (Box 3, Folder 22)
  Time in: 4:00:34 Time out: 4:24:33 Total Time: 24m 0s Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Kerouac Conference, Naropa Institute, Boulder, CO, 1982. Women's panel discussion, including Edie Kerouac Parker, Joyce Johnson, Carolyn Cassady, the panel moderator and an Italian producer, Nanda.
- Panel: Kerouac and His Women, Part II. (Box 3, Folder 23)
  Time in: 5:00:33 Time out: 5:22:31 Total Time: 21m 57s Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Kerouac Conference, Naropa Institute, Boulder, CO, 1982.Women's panel continued. Includes questions from the audience.
- Kerouac, Part I. (Box 3, Folder 24)
  Time in: 0:00:00 Time out: 0:50:09 Total Time: 50m 9s Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  A documentary by John Antonelli, 1984, with actors playing all the main Beat historical figures. An interesting combination of narrative and documentary.
  - Allen Ginsberg interview.
    Time in: 0:01:30 Time out: 0:01:40 Total Time: 0m 10s Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg talks about meeting Kerouac.
  - Allen Ginsberg interview.
    Time in: 0:16:12 Time out: 0:16:30 Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Kerouac avoided authority figures and was kicked out of the Navy.
  - Herbert Huncke interview.
    Time in: 0:18:00 Time out: 0:18:58 Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Huncke talks about Ginsberg, Kerouac and Times Square.
  - Allen Ginsberg interview.
    Time in: 0:24:44 Time out: 0:25:44 Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg on Kerouac's use of Benzedrine inhalers.
  - Allen Ginsberg interview
    Time in: 0:31:44 Time out: 0:32:33 Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg on Kerouac's archetypal characters.
  - Allen Ginsberg interview.
    Time in: 0:44:23 Time out: 0:45:07 Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg on Kerouac's writing... he was already a genius.
  - Joyce Johnson interview.
    Time in: 0:46:52 Time out: 0:48:12 Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Joyce Johnson on Ginsberg and Kerouac in New York City
- Kerouac, Part II. (Box 3, Folder 25)
  Time in: 0:00:00 Time out: 0:21:18 Total Time: 21m 18s Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master